The locals here have believed in spirits for ages .
Maybe even before there was any religion .
But , the meaning of spirits for Isan people
might not be the same as for most .
We believe everything that goes beyond nature
is all called spirits ,
not just the souls of dead people .
We believe spirits are in every single thing ,
In houses ,
in forests , in mountains ,
in trees ,
in rice fields .
Every area has spirits . All of it .
In 2018 , a documentary team traveled
all over Thailand to study the lives of shamans .
After interviewing many shamans ,
the team decided to study the life of Nim .
The shaman of ' Goddess Ba Yan ' .
For Isan people , spirits have many types ,
such as Phee Fah , Phee Tan ,
Phee Sua , Phee Ban , Phee Muang ...
They 're all spirits .
There are good spirits that protect us ,
and evil spirits
that haunt us and make us sick .
And the spirit within you , who is it ?
Let me say it in central dialect ,
They call it ' possessing . '
In Isan , they call it ' Ma Tiam . '
I 'm the shaman for Goddess Ba Yan .
Ba Yan is an ancestral spirit .
She 's a good spirit
who has protected the villages for a long time .
Actually , no one knows who She is or where She 's from .
But they 've paid respect to Her for many generations .
' Shaman Bloodline '
A documentary about the shaman inheritance in a family .
My family has been Ba Yan 's shaman for many generations .
Ever since I was born ,
I saw my grandmother as Her medium .
Ba Yan only chooses women to be Her medium .
Lots of locals would come to see us .
Every year we do a ceremony . A very big one .
The locals will ask
how the village will fare for the coming year .
After my grandmother died ,
the next person to inherit Ba Yan was my aunt .
After my aunt , the next shaman was supposed to be Noi , my elder sister ,
but Noi declined the inheritance .
Ba Yan then chose ..
Me instead .
Don 't shamans have to shake their bodies or change their voices ?
You might have watched too much TV .
It doesn 't have to be like that .
As you 've seen , people come see me every day .
Some come to heal their sickness .
Some ask for blessings or wishes .
Some repay their wishes
with offerings of a jar of liquor and a chicken .
Tell me what happened ?
My husband found this cobra and made liquor out of it .
I told him not to drink it , but he didn 't listen .
His arms and legs went numb . He doesn 't have any strength .
Where did you get it from ?
I got it from the cemetery .
This is the cause of your misery , paying for your bad karma .
Because you 're drinking the soul that resided in this animal .
Can you treat every illness ?
If someone has cancer and they come to see me ...
they will die for sure .
I can only treat illnesses that happen from the unseen
such as black magic ,
or if a spirit has harmed you , I can cure it .
But if it 's a normal illness , I advise you go see a doctor .
I never thought of being a shaman before . Actually , I didn 't want to be one .
There was a period when I was always sick .
No matter what , I couldn 't get better . It was so painful
to the point that I wanted to run away to get away from it all .
Why does it have to be me ?
But I didn 't succeed .
So I agreed to let Her take me . Actually , it is great .
Now I get to pray every day and do ceremonies .
And people come to see me , asking for help when they have troubles .
Now I consider it to be very good .
I 'm at ease .
I can 't even remember why I first didn 't accept Her ,
why I was mad at Her .
SEAMSTRESS
THE MEDIUM
We 're going to Wiroj 's funeral . Who is he ?
Wiroj is ...
the husband of my elder sister , Noi .
He found out last year that he had cancer .
I 'm sorry for your loss .
I don 't know why all the men in the Yasantia family .
Wiroj Yasantia die under bad circumstances .
Wiroj 's grandfather was stoned to death by laborers .
Wiroj 's dad , when his factory went belly-up ,
he burned the factory for insurance money .
When he was caught , he poisoned himself to death .
As for Mac , Wiroj 's eldest son ,
he died in a motorcycle accident several years ago .
How have you been ?
Haven 't seen you for so long . You 've forgotten your family ?
If no one died , we 'd never see each other .
- Is this tray ready ? - Yeah , you can take it inside .
- You always forget your relatives . - Can you stop nagging ?
He 's the pastor from the church Noi goes to .
Thank you for coming .
Mink , please get a chair for the pastor .
Mink .
How are you ?
Your mom told me you were the first one to find his body .
I 'm okay .
My family has 3 siblings .
There 's Manit , the eldest .
If you smoke a lot , you can 't tell one thing from another .
Water ? Some water ?
Noi is the middle child , and I 'm the youngest .
See ..
Wiroj , Noi 's husband , just died .
Before this , Mac , Noi 's son , passed away .
Now , Noi is left with Mink , her only daughter .
Actually , Noi and Wiroj married a bit late .
Once they married ...
Noi took over the dog meat shop from her mother-in-law ,
Wiroj 's mother .
I don 't know why she did that .
The government doesn 't allow it , but Noi still secretly does it .
My sisters , they don 't get along very well .
They have had some kind of disagreement ever since who knows when .
I 've tried to talk to them to get them to reconcile , to make up .
- Make sure they 're yours . - I won 't take someone else 's .
Thank you for coming .
Auntie .
Mom wants you to get stuff from my house .
She wrote it all down and where everything is .
Hello , Auntie Nim .
Here .
- You already closed the door , right ? - Yes .
- Lucky won 't go outside , right ? - It won 't .
You brought the wrong cloth . I wanted the thicker one .
Why don 't you go get it yourself then ?
Uncle , what the hell are you saying ?
No one said anything , Mink .
What the fuck did you say ? Say it !
I didn 't say anything .
Just mind your own business . Are you talking shit about me ? !
Who ? No one 's said anything .
- He cursed at me . - Ihaven 't done anything ...
You called me a whore !
Mink ! Stop it !
Mink , don 't !
I didn 't call you that !
Get him out of here , mom !
Mink , let 's go .
- Mink , go . Leave first . - I 'm not leaving . He cursed at me !
No one 's said anything at all .
- Dammit ! Get out of here ! - Mink , calm down .
- Mom , let go of me ! - Calm down , Mink .
He cursed at me .
He didn 't .
Does Mink usually drink a lot ?
I know she drinks , but I didn 't know it was this much .
This is the first time Mink 's caused a scene .
I see .
Go ahead .
See you around .
Drive safely .
Okay .
Mink .
Who died ?
The blind old woman whose house is behind the temple .
How did she die ?
I don 't know .
Mink .
Mink !
Wiroj ' Yasantia .
Nim , what are you doing here ?
What are you doing in Mink 's room ?
Why are you going through her things ?
I asked you a question . Why don 't you answer ?
Why aren 't you saying anything ? Gosh !
What are you looking for ? Tell me ...
Here .
See ?
Do you know what this is ?
What ?
What are you doing ? Both of you get out .
- Mink , hold on . - Mom , leave .
Mink , you 've started to have nightmares and hear strange things , right ?
No ! Nothing ! Mom , get out .
Mink ...
Get out .
Get out !
Must you film everything , seriously ?
You know what the turmeric is for , right ?
You must tell me if Mink shows any strange symptoms .
Noi !
She 's my child . I can take care of her . You should leave .
What is it that Mink hangs in her closet ?
It 's a turmeric called Pa Ta Ba .
We believe it can protect us from spirits
and other evil things .
Why the hell did they come into other people 's room ?
They went through my stuff , too . Dammit !
It 's so freaking lame .
Right ?
Why did you put the Pa Ta Ba in your room ?
What they did , it 's so childish . They 're supposed to be the adults here .
At the funeral the other day , why were you staring at that blind lady ?
What blind lady ?
Do you see someone standing over there ?
Yes .
I see someone there .
Why ?
The team went over the footage
and found Mink showing some strange behavior .
What do Mink 's recent symptoms mean ?
From what I 've gathered , they can be several things .
Does that mean Ba Yan will move to Mink ?
I don 't know .
The team had an idea . If a shaman inheritance is real ,
they might be able to record the manifestation .
They decided to film Mink and her family , too .
Hey .
Are you going to film me all the time ?
Most of the time .
Just make yourself com fortable .
Tell me about your job .
Sure .
I work at the Recruitment Center .
RECRUITMENT CENTER
All day I assign work for people to do .
Number 6 .
Hello .
I wake up at 5 a.m. I wake up early .
Eat and get into work around 7 , 8 a.m.
In the afternoon there aren 't many people . So I have some free time .
I 'm not that tired with my work .
And do you like your job ?
Yeah .
I think I 'm happy helping others find jobs .
You 're telling the truth , right ?
Of course ! I sound like a beauty queen , huh ?
How do you feel towards people who are shamans , like your aunt ?
Shamans ?
To be honest ,
I think it 's nonsense . I don 't think it 's real .
Out of the blue , they do weird dance moves . Acting like Hanuman . It 's so weird .
I 've also heard people say that there 's a Doraemon shaman .
Hilarious !
What 's a Doraemon shaman ?
Well , it 's a Doraemon shaman .
I guess when they 're taken over , they sing the theme song .
I can speak in tongues too .
I 'll show you .
See ?
Anyone can do it . Have you seen those clips ? This is how they speak . ► .
- What would you like ? - 100 baht of meat .
Thank you .
I don 't know why they won 't let us sell it .
People around here have eaten dog meat for ages .
Oh , but you sell dog meat and also have a pet dog .
Doesn 't it feel strange ?
I don 't find it strange at all .
Those who raise goldfish and carp , don 't they also eat fish ?
May I ask about Ba Yan ?
When Ba Yan tried to enter into you , can you remember how you felt at the time ?
Back then , I remember I was in my twenties .
I started to have weird symptoms .
Locals call it ' Shaman Fever . '
At the time , I had severe headaches ,
and my period came every day straight for 5 full months .
My aunt was already a shaman .
She advised me to do an Acceptance Ceremony to be a shaman .
But I didn 't want to . I didn 't like the idea of being a shaman .
So ...
I converted to Christianity .
I prayed to God
that I would not become a
that I would not become a shaman .
For if you forgive others their trespasses ,
your heavenly Father will also forgive you .
But if you do not forgive others their trespasses , neither will your Father forgive your trespasses .
But something happened with Nim , my younger sister .
Nim went to study dressmaking in the city .
They said that she fainted and blacked out
without knowing the cause .
We had to go get her and bring her back home .
After that , Ba Yan entered into Nim instead .
No one knows what happened .
Thinking about it now , I do feel guilty ...
Nim took my place as the shaman .
And what if now ...
Ba Yan wants to move to Mink . What will you do ?
If you 're going to ask me stupid questions ,
then you can stop asking .
And stop filming .
Whoa , Mink . You 're beautiful .
Why are you wearing baby shoes ?
Girl , on the parade day , you 're gonna be the prettiest .
Is it comfortable ?
It 's fine . But it 's a bit loose . They 'll take it in for me .
Oh , I see .
Lisa , have you noticed Mink acting strange lately ?
Recently , I guess you could call it strange .
It 's like she 's faking or something , like she 's not her real self .
Here , just a sec .
Mink , where are you going ?
Girl , it 's for kids . You can 't play .
I want to .
Are you out 'of your fhind ? Get out .
Mink .
Cray-cray .
Mink !
What the hell is wrong with you ?
What are you doing ?
Hey .
Can you not film me all the time ?
I 'm a mess right now .
Stop filming .
RECRUITMENT CENTER
Mink , you bitch .
You ditched me to go with some guy again ?
If you get messed up again , don 't come to me for help .
Mink ?
RECRUITMENT CENTER
I 'm here .
Oh , Mink .
Mink .
Why are you sleeping here ?
Wake up . Go wash your face and start work .
Mink .
What 's wrong ?
Mink ?
Where did you sleep last night ? I called , but you didn 't pick up .
It 's time you stop drinking .
Mink .
What 's with you ?
It 's just my period . What 's with the nagging ?
Wait , talk to me first . For how long ?
Mink !
Talk to me . Has it been long since you 've had it ?
- Pang , where 's Manit ? - He went out to meet friends .
- Do you know who ? - No idea .
Manit !
What are you doing here ?
Don 't you give a shit about your wife and kid ?
Get up and come with me . I need to talk to you about something .
Now !
Right now , Mink 's symptoms are like yours and Nim 's back then , right ?
That 's right .
You must have Nim do the Acceptance Ceremony for Mink .
You know I don 't want my child to be a shaman .
But if Ba Yan really wants Mink , what can you do ?
- I don 't know what I have to do . - Think it over .
What the hell is it with you ?
Calm down , sweetie .
- Stop being nosy , hag ! - Hey ! Why are you doing that ?
- What are you doing ? ! - Stop the car !
- Get off ! - No !
- Stop ! - Isaid I 'm not getting off !
- Have you lost it ? - Damn all of you !
You !
- Get lost ! - Come on , let 's go .
Damn you !
Damn all of you .
Shit .
Dammit .
Why the hell did they chase me off ? Assholes .
I hope you all die .
I hope all of you die .
Is this all you got ?
Yes .
Has Mink ever acted strange , like she 's someone else ?
Well , she sometimes acts like a kid .
Anything else , aside from acting like a kid ?
From our footage , there isn 't anything else .
- Have you seen my beaded bracelet ? - Oh .
It might have fallen off here , when I came to get things for Noi .
- What bracelet ? - My brown bracelet .
- The one you always wear , right ? - Yeah .
Where did you go that day ?
I came to get the meds here , and I went up to Noi 's room to get the scarf .
It might have fallen off there . Noi , go up and take a look for Nim .
It isn 't around here .
I really need to use it . Could you please take a look for me ?
Look thoroughly .
Mink .
Mink , are you okay ?
Recently , have you heard someone calling you ?
And did you happen to answer them ?
- There has been , right ? - Nim ! What are you talking to her ?
They 're not talking about anything . Just small talk between aunt and niece .
What did you say to her ?
Nothing .
- You told her to come , didn 't you ? - What are you talking about ?
She came looking for her bracelet It fell off the day she came to get your stuff .
Mink .
Fine , I 'm leaving now .
Mink , what is it ?
What did auntie say ?
What did she talk to you about ?
What is it ?
Mom .
Tell me .
Mom , I don 't want to be a shaman .
I won 't let you be one . I won 't let it happen .
- Don 't be afraid . - You have to help me .
- Don 't be afraid . - Mom , you have to help me .
Why do you think Nim came to see Mink ?
She wants Mink to replace her as a shaman .
She doesn 't have any children .
But no matter what , I won 't let my child be a shaman .
Ms. Kanda Yasantia . Receive your medicine at counter 2 .
I 'll get it for you . Wait here .
I 've got headaches . It feels like my head 's gonna explode .
Stomachaches . Backaches .
And that part also hurts .
When it hurts ..
It feels like it 's going to rip apart .
The doctor said he doesn 't know what 's wrong either .
He doesn 't know the cause .
Have you dreamed of anything strange lately ?
I have the same dream repeatedly almost every night .
In my dreams , I see a huge man .
He 's wearing a red loin cloth and a red vest with some kind of talisman all over it .
In my dreams ...
he 's holding a long sword .
He stomps his foot
and licks the blood from the sword .
And ..
There 's a decapitated head and blood all over the floor .
It 's like the head is trying to tell me something .
And what is the head saying ?
I try to listen to what it 's saying . But ...
there isn 't any sound that comes out .
Mink .
Are you okay ?
Leave me alone !
Mink , can you get up ?
Can you get up ?
Come on .
Get out !
I think we should go to the hospital . Let 's go .
Leave me alone . Get out !
May I have a word with you ?
You can 't film anymore .
What the fuck are you saying ? !
How can you fire me ? Asshole !
Screw you !
Mink .
- Did you take your meds this morning ? - Mink !
- Will you be okay ? - Mink , come change .
I 'll be outside .
Done . Wait for us to do your hair .
Mink ?
Hey !
GOD REMAINS WITH US
Mink .
Whoa , she 's so gorgeous .
Why doesn 't she look at us ?
Mink !
BORDER CROSSING POINT
Where are you going now ?
To work .
What are you doing here ?
Get out !
Security !
Get her out of here .
The thing is ...
stuff in our office went missing .
So I took a look at the CCTV .
Sumeth Recruitment Center Director
and found this .
As you can see ..
Look .
Disgusting .
This woman is shameless .
Mink .
Are you taking a shower ?
Mink !
Noi ?
Manit !
What is it , Noi ?
Oh , God !
Shit !
Go get some towels . Noi , call the doctor .
Hurry , call an ambulance . Get me some towels .
Shit !
Noi !
Be careful .
It 's the hospital , right ? Send an ambulance right away .
What happened ?
Why ?
Nim .
I now surrender .
I 'll let Mink do the Acceptance Ceremony .
Please hold the Acceptance Ceremony for Mink .
I don 't want to see my child like this .
Mink can 't do the Acceptance Ceremony .
Why not ?
Because what 's taken hold of Mink isn 't Ba Yan .
How come it 's not ?
Mink 's symptoms are like what you and I had .
If Mink agrees to become a shaman , her symptoms will disappear too , right ?
I can 't let Mink do the ceremony .
You have to do it for Mink .
Manit , come with me .
Nim .
I 'm gonna go with Nim then .
Nim , you have to do it for her .
She 's your niece . Don 't you pity her ?
Open the door .
Open what door ?
- This door . - What are you going to do ?
Hurry , will you ?
Are you sure ?
Tell me first , what are you gonna do ?
Tell me the truth . How did Mac really die ?
Everyone knows that his motorcycle flipped over .
Tell me the truth .
I know ...
Mink and Mac had something going on .
Do you know
what the soul of someone who commits suicide becomes ?
Do you ?
Tell me where Mac killed himself ?
The team agrees with Nim 's judgment .
They believe Mink is possessed by ' something else '
Sit down slowly .
Now that Nim won 't do the Acceptance Ceremony for Mink , do you know what you 're going to do next ?
If she won 't help me ,
I 'll find my own way .
Even if ..
It may go against my religion .
I must do it .
Mac !
Tell me .
All of this is your doing , right ?
I know that you love her , but you can 't take her .
Do you hear me ?
Are you really going to do this , Noi ?
Yeah , just drive .
Get the stuff and come upstairs .
All right .
Stop right now !
Stop ! I said stop !
Stop !
Nim .
- Stop it ! - Why are you doing this ? !
How could you do a random ceremony like this ? !
What if she receives some evil spirit ?
What do you expect me to do ? She is about to die .
- You won 't help me . - You don 't understand .
Why wouldn 't I help you ?
- I have my own way . - When are you gonna help me ?
- Why did you do the ceremony with this man ? - You want me to watch my child die ?
Do you know who he is ?
Mink .
When are you going to help ? Are you going to let her die ?
Mink ! Stop it , Mink !
Mink !
Mink , stop !
Stop !
Mink !
Mink .
Nim .
What about Mink ?
Mink .
- Where 's Mink , Nim ? - Lie down . Lie down , first .
What about Mink ?
Did you find Mink ? Did you find her ?
Oh , Mink .
Why is she like this , Nim ?
You have to help Mink .
You have to help her , Nim .
The only way to find her is to hold a ceremony .
But first things first , Noi must open her heart
to accept Ba Yan ,
and beg for Her forgiveness ,
even if she once shunned Ba Yan away ,
which is a serious matter .
But I believe She will have mercy on Noi .
Lift it above your head .
If Noi really opens her heart to Her ,
Ba Yan will definitely forgive her .
Give the offerings to Her .
What 's that smell ?
Go through it all .
We have to gather all the foul things Mink 's collected from various places
and do a ceremony .
What is this ? Take a look .
Because in these things , there are traces of the spirits Mink came in contact with .
Nim . Look here .
She even kept this under the bed .
She has baby shoes , too .
Nim .
Take everything out of here .
Take it all away .
And we must do the ceremony where Mac killed himself .
I 'll have to pray to Mac not to harm Mink .
I have to let Mac know ,
even if he loved Mink , or was mad and seeking revenge on this family ,
I won 't let him do anything to her .
Actually , I don 't even know how much longer I have to pray .
No matter how long it takes , I 'll just keep doing it .
Until I know where Mac took Mink .
A taxi saw the announcement .
So he gave the clip from his dashcam to the police .
The driver said that he picked Mink up around 3 a.m.
When she got in ,
he asked her questions , but she didn 't answer .
After that , you can see what happened in the clip .
Hey .
Where are you going ?
Hey !
What the hell ?
Fine , I 'm gonna leave now .
Shit !
Dammit .
Maybe this clip is edited ?
I had someone take a look at the scene .
There hasn 't been any other leads on Mink .
If there is any more news , I 'll let you know .
I 'm worried for my daughter .
I don 't know where she is now , alive or dead .
All I can do is pray ...
to the Lord
and any other gods out there .
Please bring my daughter back to me .
I already went everywhere .
Everyone 's house , all her friends ' houses , all her ex 's .
I went everywhere , but no one 's seen her .
I 've prayed and done everything I could .
If it had worked , she 'd be back by now .
HEAVENLY MEAT
SEAMSTRESS TEMPORARILY CLOSED
Ever since Mink disappeared , everyone in the family is miserable ,
especially Noi .
She can 't eat or sleep at all .
A month has already passed . We haven 't received any news .
Are you wasting taxpayers ' money ? !
- It 's not like that . - Police are all the same !
- It 's not like that . - No matter which station .
It 's been a month already . All I see is you sitting around .
You guys just sit around .
- I don 't see you doing anything . - They 're working , sir .
I just see you with your eyes open , that 's all . Is this what you call working ?
There hasn 't been any more news .
Nothing .
No news , no leads from anywhere at all .
I 've been completely tricked so far .
It 's done by the ones that have nothing to do with Mac .
Then , who are they ?
YASANTIA THREAD FACTORY
Mink .
Mink , wake up .
Right now , the patient is safe ,
but she might be malnourished .
She has bruises and scratches , but they 're not so bad .
Will my daughter go back to normal again ?
When the patient regains consciousness , we 'll reevaluate her symptoms .
Right now , things are becoming clearer .
It 's a good thing that it didn 't kill Mink .
I 'm going to go up the mountain again .
I have to pray and beg Ba Yan once more .
Who did this to you , Ba Yan ?
Where did you go ? What did you do ? Tell me .
Try to take at least one bite .
It didn 't even go in her mouth .
Mink is now completely possessed .
Who are you ?
I asked , who are you ?
I 'm Ba Yan .
I asked , who are you ? !
Why don 't you guess who I am ?
Try guessing .
Hey ! What 's with you ? !
Mink !
Have you lost it ? !
You 're crazy !
Why is she like this ?
Mink !
Don 't you like young girls ' pussies ? Don 't you like it ? !
Why are you doing this ? !
Mink !
Mink , why are you doing this ?
- Get her off . - Let go of me !
- Get her off . - Let me go !
Mink .
- Hold her down . - Let go !
- Why are you like this ? - Let go !
Hold her down . Quick .
Put her index finger in the glass !
Mink .
You know ...
the reason you 're like this
is because of your beloved sister .
She planned to get you to wear her clothes every day .
She put talismans in your shoes .
She did everything
to get you to be the shaman instead of her .
Did you know ?
Go find something to tie her up with . Hurry !
Tie her up tightly .
Hurry up .
Hurry ! When you 're done , get out .
Get out first .
Stop filming already .
Get out ! Out !
Everyone , get out .
I need to find someone to help me .
Nim .
About what Mink just said ...
I 'm sorry .
It 's fine . I 'm going to help her anyway .
Santi .
Are you still involved with these clowns ?
I still have to make a living , you know .
Mink .
Hey , wait .
You guys ..
Took her to do some random Acceptance Ceremony , right ?
Mink 's condition right now ...
is like a car that has the key left in it .
Anyone can drive it anywhere .
And who is this spirit ?
It 's not just one .
I don 't know who they are .
If you want me to count how many , it 's also impossible .
All I know is that ...
they 're all in it together because they 're vindictive .
And it 's this vengeance ...
that attracted all the wandering ghosts as well as the lost spirits of beasts ...
such as snakes , dogs , centipedes , spiders ...
and those of plants and grass .
All of them have gathered together and become a very powerful , evil demon .
Right here .
This is where I found Mink .
We 'll conduct the ceremony right here ,
where all the evil spirits originated from .
If we can get rid of them all , their slivers in Mink will also disappear .
And why does it have to be Mink ?
Do you know about the ancestors of your husband 's family ?
Wiroj 's ancestors beheaded thousands of people .
The last wishes of those dying people were to curse the family ,
and their children and offspring never stopped making bad karma .
And Wiroj ...
married you .
The one who rejected Ba Yan .
From then on ...
everything was destined to be that
the one who has to pay redemption is Mink .
Do you think it 's reasonable ?
About what Santi said , that everything was destined .
You don 't have to worry . We 'll get the auspicious date soon .
Destined by who ?
God ?
Buddha ?
Other deities ?
If it 's the ancestors that created bad karma ,
why does Mink have to pay for it ? Why not me ?
Go sit over there first .
You don 't have to think too much .
Once the ceremony is done , Mink will get better .
Ba Yan will help us .
Back then , when I was sick ,
everyone said Ba Yan was going to possess me .
But I didn 't feel anything .
Was just sick .
Let me ask you something .
Have you ever seen Ba Yan ?
Is there really a Ba Yan ?
Of course , there is .
Have you ever seen Her ?
No .
Then how do you know ?
I can feel it .
I can feel Her .
You have to believe in Ba Yan ,
and She will help us .
To perform this ceremony ,
the more evil and dangerous the spirits are , the more I have to be prepared .
I have to make lots of talismans and consecrate them all ,
including a sacred wand .
I consecrate them over and over with all the power I have .
And I also have to prepare holy water , candles , and incense .
It 's really an extravagant affair .
Most importantly , I have to do the ceremony with Nim .
Nim and I have to be united as one . It 's really tough , but it 's challenging .
Although , I 've been doing this for a long time . Let 's see how tough they are .
She won 't eat anything .
When I talk with her , she 's not receptive .
I 'm really stressed out .
Nim hasn 't come either . She 's been busy with the ceremony preparations .
One other thing ...
every morning when I come down , the house is a total mess .
It must be Mink . She does it every night .
I don 't know what she does .
The team decided to install cameras inside the house
to observe Mink 's behavior at night .
6 days before the ceremony .
Lucky .
What 's wrong , Lucky ?
5 days before the ceremony
4 days before the ceremony
3 days before the ceremony .
If you set up cameras everywhere like this , then no more filming .
- Manit ... - Pack your stuff and go ! I won 't allow it !
I 'm asking you , please watch till the very end .
- Please . - What ?
Why is she like this ?
If she 's become crazy like this , how can we keep living together ?
You can go live wherever you want .
I 'm staying here with my child .
I admit that ...
it looks scary .
But she 's still my child .
It won 't be long till she gets better .
Nim will help her .
Nim is an expert . She 's helped lots of people .
She can definitely help Mink .
Don 't you think ?
After seeing Mink 's behavior ,
the family members allowed the team to install more cameras .
My stomach hurts .
2 days before the ceremony .
Done .
She can 't get out anymore .
She can only dream of getting out .
That 's it . Let 's go . All done .
Mink !
Guys , wake up !
You need to get up !
Holy shit .
Pong !
Mink !
- Pong ! - What is it , Manit ?
Where is Pong ? !
- What is it ? - Mink took Pong !
Mink took my son !
Where did she take him ?
Let 's go look .
- She took my son . - Where did she take Pong ? !
Mink .
Let 's go find him .
Pong !
Where did she take him ?
Come on . Let 's go search .
Mink !
Why did you take my kid ?
Have you lost it ? !
Mink .
Mink !
Have you seen Mink ?
No .
Mink !
Dammit ! Why are you doing this ?
Mink ! Where are you ?
Mink !
Pong .
Pong !
My boy .
It 's all right now , baby .
Mink ?
Mink !
Mink .
What the hell ? !
Mink !
Mink .
Let go of him .
1 day before the ceremony .
Nim .
Is something wrong ?
I 've been calling her since last night , but she hasn 't answered .
I can hear her phone ringing inside . Why won 't she answer it ?
I 'll go get help .
Okay .
Nim .
Nim !
Where are you ? !
Nim .
Why are there so many maggots ?
Nim !
Wake up .
Why are you sleeping like this ?
Nim !
Hurry , come help me !
I don 't know what 's with her ! Quick ! Nim !
Nim died while asleep .
Isan people call it , ' Lai Tai ' .
Doctors could not conclude the cause of death .
Nim died because of me .
Mink is like this because of me .
I have no one left in my life .
From now on ,
I 'm going to do everything to protect my daughter from harm .
I 'm even willing to die .
Why did Nim die ? The spirits did it , right ?
There 's no way we can know .
What 's that supposed to mean ?
Why are you saying such things ?
Master , what are we supposed to do now ?
Don 't worry .
Tomorrow , we will conduct the ceremony as planned .
Day of ceremony .
- Put it here ? - Yeah , put it over there .
Master Santi , please tell us about today 's ceremony .
The ceremony will take place on the 5th floor .
The first thing I have to do is
summon the evil spirits to gather
into Mink 's body .
Then
I 'll expel the spirits
into the cursed pot .
And I 'll take the pot to the ground floor , bury it , and perform a spellbinding ritual .
Based on what happened to Nim ,
will it be too risky to let Mink still be a part of the ceremony ?
Well , yeah .
But ...
have you noticed the back of Manit 's car ?
It has a sticker that says ..
" This car is red . "
THIS CAR IS RED
What does that have to do with the ceremony ?
Don 't let anyone
leave the area of the ceremony at all ,
until the ceremony is over .
Come and eat !
Come on ! Come and get it !
Come !
Why did she scream ?
I don 't know .
Noi !
- Noi . - How is she ?
- She 's just blacked out . - Take her to rest up .
Noi !
How are you , Noi ?
Can you hear me ?
Is there anyone out there ?
Why am I being locked up ?
Mom ? Are you outside ?
Please open the door .
Did the spirit leave already ?
I don 't know .
Pong ?
Mink .
Pong , open the door for me .
Mink !
You 're better now , right ?
Open the door .
She 's well now , right ?
Pang , I 'm in here .
Open the door , please .
I don 't know .
The Master told us not to open the door if the ceremony isn 't over .
- Please open the door . - Mink .
Open the door for me , please . I 'm locked up in here .
Hold on .
- Pang , please open the door . - Mink .
No one has called to let us know yet .
Pang . Where are all of you ? Pang ?
Mink .
Pang , open the door .
Mink , are you okay ?
Mink .
Pong .
Open the door . My son is in there .
- We can 't . - Open it !
Open it ! My son is in there !
We can 't . No matter what , we can 't open it .
He 's in there ! Can 't you hear him ? Huh ? !
How can that be ?
I just saw your son in the crib .
He 's in there ! Are you deaf ? !
My son 's in there . Pong !
Master Santi ordered us not to open it .
- Take a look in the crib for me . - Mink ! Please don 't do anything to Pong !
Open the door .
- I can 't . - Open it right now !
Go look in the crib for me .
Open it !
Open it , dammit !
- Go look in the crib ! - Okay !
Open it !
Pang !
You can 't go in !
Pong !
Pang !
Master , why do you stop here ?
Master ?
What the hell ?
Master !
Master , what 's wrong ?
No ! Master !
Pong !
Mink .
Where is Pong ?
Shit !
Open up .
Open the door !
Help !
Help me !
I can 't open it .
Don 't .
No !
Shit !
Why did the lights go out ?
Turn on the camera 's light .
Okay .
Shit .
Where did everyone go ?
Hey .
What happened ?
Where is everybody ?
Hey .
Let 's get the hell out of here .
Fuck this !
Shit , so damn dark ...
Holy shit .
Oh , hell .
Manit !
Noi .
Manit .
Are you all right ?
Are you okay ?
I can feel it now .
Ba Yan is with me now .
Ba Yan is here to help me .
The ceremony must be continued .
Go get the potsherd .
We 'll perform the spellbinding ritual once again .
Go ! Hurry !
Give me the incense .
Can I film you instead ?
Why did she put them in that way ?
No , no , no !
Manit , don 't !
No !
You , evil spirit ,
leave my child 's body now .
You 're going to surrender now
to the mighty power of Ba Yan !
Mom .
Mink .
Mink , it 's you , right ?
It 's you , right ?
Mink .
Please return my child .
Give me back my child .
Return her ...
Mink .
Can you hear me ?
Mink , are you still in there ?
Mink .
Don 't ...
Don 't do it .
Don 't do this to me .
Mink .
Can you hear me ?
Mink ! I 'm sorry .
I 'm sorry .
Come back to me , Mink .
Mink .
God , please help Mink .
Mink , don 't give up hope .
Don 't do this .
Don 't do this to me .
' Yasantia '
Nim 's last interview .
What just happened in front of the altar ?
I was just thinking of ...
the day of the ceremony , I don 't know what will happen .
Why ?
Any problems with the preparations ?
It might mean nothing at all .
What do you mean ?
Honestly ...
I 've never really known ..
I was never really sure ...
if Ba Yan actually possessed me or not .
What do you mean ?
I don 't know anymore .